[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
What about Cha Dohyun?
What?
I mean, is he doing well?
We broke up.
Ah...
It's already summer.
Why don't you take a shower at my place?
What?
Hey, Kwon Yihyun.
I'm saying this because I'm worried.
Don't talk like this to other people.
What?
I'm saying this 'cause who knows—
you didn't... have feelings... for me, right?
If you think we can get together just 'cause I broke up with him,
it'll put me in a tight spot.
Forget it if you're not.
Why are you looking at me like that? Jeez.
I'm off.
Hey, Kwon Yihyun.
Those people at the club won't do anything strange
like bullying you, right?
No.
That's good enough.
I'm off for real.
[Sung Inho]
[Kim Domin]
[Summertime]
[3 months ago]
[Cha Dohyun]
Do you know where this is?
Just go in that direction.
Thank you.
Cha Dohyun, I'm here.
The drinking snacks are here!
Oh... It's Yeo Eunho.
Here.
Who's this?
Someone you know?
Yeah,
he's my favorite person in the world.
What? You have someone like that?
Hello, I'm Dohyun's friend in the same major.
I'll get going.
Hey, Cha Dohyun!
Darn it.
You're a freshman, don't you know your place?
How dare you leave when your seniors are here?
Hey, come back later.
I want to leave.
Do I need a reason not to leave?
What did this rascal say?
You're drunk.
Don't stop me!
I'm not drunk, darn it!
He always looks down on me.
Feels damn ass!
Let go of me!
What are you doing? Just go!
Where are you? Why did you leave alone?
What? Managed to leave?
Yes.
Who was that?
The class representative.
He went to the military as soon as he got into college.
It's his first semester back.
He was probably drunk.
Isn't that your senior?
Of course.
Don't be like that. It's not too late. Go back.
If you offend those old brats,
you'll be the one to suffer.
I put the side dishes in the fridge.
Don’t drink too much.
Eunho. Seems like you don't miss me that much.
What?
You've been saying you're busy and tired lately.
We haven't seen each other for a long time.
Are you drunk?
Is that all you can say?
Hey. I'm just worried that you offend your senior.
What's more, make it clear.
People might think we haven't met for months.
It's only been 4 days. Four!
So?
We met 4 days ago,
so it's fine that we don't see each other?
Fine.
I'm sorry I was too busy. Darn it, are you satisfied now?
It's all my fault, okay?
Bye.
I'll get this too.
[Hangover drink]
It's 8,700 won.
[Condom]
Excuse me,
-I'm the one here first... -We'll get this too.
What? Why are you here?
'Cause you said you were sorry.
What?
So I came to accept your apology.
Do you want to pay for this too?
No, we don't know each other.
Hey.
Is it fun to tease me?
I don't like to tease you.
I like you.
Sweet-talker.
Mom worked so hard.
Tell her we'll visit her next week.
Aren't you her son?
Call her yourself, you unfilial son.
What's all this? Why did you buy so much?
It's all for me. Don't touch it.
I'll kill you if you eat any.
Fine.
But...
Can I eat something else?
Again?
The class representative
poured soju in a beer cup and told me to drink it up.
Stop it. You're sweating.
I gave him some suggestions
for one of our group assignments this time, so he might be picking me
cause I ticked him off.
It’s so annoying, Eunho.
So what do you want me to do?
Can you comfort me today?
What?
Let's shower together.
No, I'm tired.
Then just stay still.
Stop it.
Touch me too.
[Forum]
[I saw a handsome guy smoking at the business administration building.]
[I wanted to chat him up by asking him for fire but he gave me the lighter straight. Seriously speaking: he wants to marry me, right?]
[I wanted to ask for his phone number, but he left picking up a phone call all smiles.]
[Since he was at the business administration building, that must be his major right? I'm going to camp there for him starting today.]
[204 replies]
[Anonymous 1: I'm sure he has a girlfriend.]
[Anonymous 2: There's only one person they can be talking about if it's business administration.]
[Anonymous 3: I'm from another department, but I can guess who it is. There has been so many posts like this since school started.]
[Anonymous 4: Haha, my friend already got his number.]
[Messages] [Yeo Eunho: Where are you?]
[Kim Minhyuk: Dohyon, do you wanna meet my friend?] [Seo Taeyoung: My friend asked me for your number.]
[Nam Soo-a: Do you want to go on a blind date?] [Ji Soyeon: Dohyun, my friend says she's interested in you.]
What are you going to do tomorrow?
To help out at my parents' place.
Then I won't see you tomorrow?
Mm.
Why?
Can't we meet tomorrow too?
No.
Well,
the girl who flirted with you when you were smoking,
was she pretty?
Seems like she was your type.
You even gave her a lighter.
Eunho.
What?
Are you jealous?
I was just asking.
I'm not jealous.
I didn't want to keep a lighter someone else has touched,
so I gave it to her.
How can you still not know what my type is?
Hmm?
Should I tell you while washing you up?
Just sleep, you pervert.
Dohyun.
Hmm?
You're the only one I like.
What? Are you confessing?
You like a lot of things, and you're very capable.
Don't worry.
I only have you.
Check please!
Okay, I'll get you your check.
Which table is it?
The one over there.
Over there.
Do you need a receipt?
The meat is burning!
Hold on.
Please excuse me.
Sorry.
I'll get you a new plate of meat.
Here's your beer.
I wanted soju.
I'm sorry. I'll get it right away.
[Missed call: Cha Dohyun]
Please leave a message after the tone.
After...
[Cha Dohyun: Done with my day. Arrived at our stay!]
Eunho, charcoal!
Okay. Coming.
Smells good.
-It smells good, right? -Yes.
Jihyun made all of them.
I just cut the vegetables.
That's everything.
Where's Dohyun?
He said he'll be late cause he has student council meeting.
Let's eat first.
-Okay. -All right.
Yeo Eunho, come out!
Is Dohyun the year representative?
Yes.
I heard he got a scholarship too.
If you become an intern in sophomore year,
you can go straight to the company after you graduate.
Dohyun has nothing to worry about.
What about Eunho?
What have you been up to lately?
He's been helping out at the store.
You're helping your parents— that's amazing.
It's nothing much.
What did you like again?
What was your dream when you were young?
He has to take over this shop.
Why?
What?
You never asked me if I wanted to take over.
What are you going to do if not that?
Do you have other plans?
Well,
kids at his age must have a lot they want to do.
That's why he doesn't know what he wants to do.
You'll get used to it doing it.
It makes you feel like this is your dream.
Goodbye.
Welcome...
My son! You're here.
These are my college classmates.
This is my mom. Say hello.
Hello.
Welcome.
Eunho.
Set up the tableware.
Oh!
You're that deliveryman, right?
You met him in front of the major activity room that day, right?
He's my favorite friend.
You've got something on your face.
I'm sorry. Sorry.
What? For what?
For everything.
Seems like you saw
how embarrassed I was.
Eunho, it’s not like that.
Whether it's back in school or now,
when I'm with you,
I'm always the worse off one.
It was already enough that you got me to go to your school.
Why do you have to come to the store?
I'm sorry.
This was thoughtless of me.
I came here cause I just
wanted to see you, no matter what.
You selfish jerk.
You're always
so selfish.
Yeo Eunho.
Just find someone as good as you.
I never thought that way.
I know you did nothing wrong.
It's my fault.
Let's stop here.
What did you say?
I said let's break up.
[Summertime]
By the way, Eunho.
A part-timer is joining tomorrow.
A part-timer?
Who?
He's going to do it for just a month.
You have to do it lightly so it doesn't look unfresh.
What? Not going to work?
I have something to say, Yeo Eunho.
Do we have anything to say to each other?
I'm off.
Yeo Eunho, come out.
I'm dying from the heat, so come out.